<Document>
# Exploding Butlers
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingEyesMonocle" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="DrinkTeapot" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RagItem" Caption=""/>
</Box>

<Box>
  [color=#999999][italic]They're butlers that explode.[/italic][/color]
</Box>
  
## Rules
Butlers are [color=cyan]Familiars[/color], bound to their objectives:

1. Serve their target

Though it is ultimately up to their master to determine what tasks must be fulfilled, in the absence of orders, a Butler must remain dignified and service-driven. 
They are licensed professionals, given [color=green]service access[/color] to properly be able to anticipate the needs of their employer—whether that be tea, coffee, or perhaps something a bit stronger.
Butlers are not the martial sort. [bold]It would be improper to seek out violent acts without direct instruction.[/bold] 
Even then, their frail arms will [color=red]struggle to wield[/color] any weapon or gear that requires two hands.

2. Die a Butler death

It would be the most despicable betrayal for a Butler to survive to the end of their most anticipated day. 
When the timing is right, an inexperienced employer may need prompting as to the function of their remote signaller. The butler, whether pathetic, delicate, refined, or calculating, knows best how to inform them of their responsibility. With all due respect, of course.

As with all other Familiars, Butlers do the bidding of their master, regardless of what that may be. If their master is an antagonist, they can be asked to do antagonistic things. Despite their allegiance, scheming is best left to true villians, and [color=red]Butlers cannot choose to do antagonistic things on their own.[/color]

## Care Package
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BoxButler" Caption="Care Package"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RemoteSignallerButler" Caption="Detonation Device"/>
  </Box>
Selected by the [color=yellow]Sirs Collective[/color] to have your own Butler? You should receive a care package via bluespace delivery.

Be sure to keep the butler detonation device on your person. Such an important responsibility [color=yellow]must not be misplaced[/color]. 

</Document>
