<Document>
  # Moth People

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobMoth" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  Moths are somewhat unique among NT-accepted species, in that they have no commonly-accepted species name. Due to the lack of Earth moths aboard NT vessels and stations, most people are content with referring to them simply as Moths.

  Their wings don't allow them to fly under Earthlike gravity (as is generated by NT's proprietary Gravity Generators,) but [color=#1e90ff]under low gravity, they are capable of greater acceleration.[/color] Of course, this does not make them capable of unassisted space flight - but [color=#1e90ff]their skill and experience may make them more efficient fliers while using jetpacks.[/color]

  ## Dietary Restrictions
  Their unique mouthparts and dietary needs render them [color=#ffa500]incapable of consuming the same foods as other humanoids.[/color] Instead, [color=#1e90ff]Moths must eat textiles - cotton, fabric, or clothing.[/color] Some NT Chefs have developed specialty recipies to cater to their needs, since [color=#ffa500]some of the harsher chemicals that humans enjoy (like theobromine and allicin) have proven unpleasant for them.[/color]
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="YarnNoodles" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  ## Damage

  [color=yellow][bold]NOTE:[/bold][/color] Species damage modifiers work largely the same way worn armor does, primarily applying to external, direct sources of damage. Unless explicitly stated, these [color=yellow][bold]do not[/bold][/color] apply to intrinsic sources of damage, such extreme pressure, extreme body temperature, or metabolizing chemicals.

  Due to their fluffy carapace, they are insulated from the cold, and take [color=#1e90ff]30% less Cold damage, have a higher tolerance for cold temperatures, and take half as much Cold damage from low body temperatures.[/color] However, this also causes them to take [color=#ffa500]20% more Heat damage, catch on fire more easily, have a lower tolerance for warm temperatures, and take twice as much Heat damage from high body temperatures.[/color]

  # Moth Naming Conventions

  Moths typically use Human-adjacent first names and light or nature themed last names.
  - [color=#449944]Acceptable:[/color] Socrates Temnora
  - [color=#449944]Acceptable:[/color] Sierra Lightseeker
  - [color=#449944]Acceptable:[/color] James Nightflitter
  - [color=#994444]Bad:[/color] Benry

</Document>
